1stbrowser.com 2015-06-24

# Privacy ∴ 1st Browser

SIEN privacy policy

1st Browser

_Last Updated Date: 06-20-2013_

SIEN provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of 1stbrowser.com (the “ **Site** ”) and SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER (collectively the “ **Application** ”).

SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER is SIEN S.A. proprietary software that provides and Internet browser who facilitates access and use of connected services as (but not limited to) browsing, content usage and sharing, news feed. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site and from your use of the Application. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible at: [http://www.1stbrowser.com/corporate/terms/](http://www.1stbrowser.com/corporate/terms/).

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

**Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, the Application and features and content relating thereto (together, the “ **Service** ”) and to enable users to enjoy the Service.

·         In order to access certain features of the Service, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your username and email address. Your username does not have to be your real name, it will be whatever name you choose as your username, however it will be deemed Personal Information if it is your real name. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service to you and administer your inquiries.

·         We collect other information when you visit the Site and/or install one or more of the Application components, including your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or version, operating system type or version or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site and by using the Application, access times and dates, usage statistics for your use of the Application and other statistics (“ **Non-Identifying Information** ”). We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Application and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site and Application’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Site and Application to our visitors’ needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site or use the Application, it will recognize you and serve accurate search results, advertisements and other information to you appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to localize your usage of the Services and make appropriate adaptations on country by country basis. We do not treat Non-Identifying Information as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

·         Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers in a way that enables you to be identified (for example, combining your browser type with your email address). But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other SIEN users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

**SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER**

The SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER includes an update feature that checks SIEN's servers periodically to ensure that you are running latest version of our browser (which is the most stable, secure and feature-rich version of the SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER).

Like most Web sites, our servers automatically record the page requests made when you visit our sites. These “server logs” typically include your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

·         The Internet Protocol address assigned to the user by the user’s ISP; depending on the user’s service, a different address may be assigned to the user by their service provider each time they connect to the Internet

·         The date and time of the query

·         The requested URL, including the search query

·         The browser and operating system being used

·         The unique cookie ID assigned to this particular computer the first time it visited SIEN's web site(s). (Cookies can be deleted by users. If the user has deleted the cookie from the computer since the last time s/he visited SIEN's web site(s), then it will be the unique cookie ID assigned to the user the next time s/he visits SIEN's web site(s) from that particular computer).

In addition, some SIEN Browser features send limited additional information to SIEN:

·         Queries typed in the adress bar as in the search pages

Information stored on your computer when you use SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER: SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER records useful information about your browsing history on your own computer. This includes:

·         Basic browsing history information: the URLs of pages that you visit, a cache file of text from those pages, and a list of some IP addresses linked from pages that you visit.

·         A searchable index of most pages you visit (except for secure pages with "https" web addresses, such as some bank pages)

·         Thumbnail-sized screenshots of most pages you visit

·         Cookies or web storage data deposited on your machine by websites you visit

·         A record of downloads you have made from websites

·         You can delete all or portions of this history (cf. the "Delete your browsing history" chapter)

Delete your browsing history

·         Clear your entire browsing history

·         Click the wrench icon on the browser toolbar.

·         Select Tools.

·         Select Clear browsing data.

·         In the dialog that appears, select the "Clear browsing history" checkbox.

·         Use the "Clear data from this period" menu to select the amount of data you want to delete. Select everything to clear your entire browsing history.

·         Click Clear browsing data.

Information that gets removed when you clear your entire browsing history, the following information is removed from SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER and your computer:

·         Web addresses you've visited, listed on the History page

·         Cached text of pages you've visited

·         Snapshots of your most frequently visited pages

·         Any IP addresses pre-fetched from pages you've visited

Clear specific items from your browsing history

·         Click the wrench icon on the browser toolbar.

·         Select History.

·         Click Edit items on the blue bar at the top of the page.

·         Select the checkboxes for the items you'd like to remove.

·         Click Remove selected items.

·         Click “Done” removing items on the blue bar at the top of the page to return to your normal view.

Clear your browsing history from the address bar

To prevent matches to your browsing history from appearing in the address bar, follow the steps above to clear your entire browsing history.

You can also limit the information SIEN’S 1st BROWSER saves on your computer by using incognito mode. In this mode, the browser will not store basic browsing history information such as URLs, cached page text, or IP addresses of pages linked from the websites you visit. It will also not store snapshots of pages that you visit or keep a record of your downloads. (This information could still be stored elsewhere on your computer, though.) New cookies received in incognito mode will not be saved after you close your browser or return to normal browsing mode. You can see when you are in incognito mode because the incognito icon appears in the top corner of your browser; in some cases the border of your browser window may also change color.

When you make changes to your browser configuration, such as by bookmarking a web page or changing your settings, this information is also saved. These changes are not affected by incognito mode.

You can choose to have SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER save your passwords for specific websites. Stored passwords can be reviewed in the Personal Stuff tab of the Options dialog box.

**Privacy preferences**

You can control all your privacy preferences for SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER from the Options dialog, under the Privacy section located at the top of the Under the Hood tab.

**COOKIES – SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER related elements**

You have complete control when it comes to cookie permissions in SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER. All cookies are allowed by default, but you can adjust this setting. If cookies have been set or blocked on the page you’re viewing, an icon appears at the end of the address bar.

Adjust cookie permissions

·         Click the wrench icon on the SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER toolbar.

·         Select “Options”

·         Click the Under the Hood tab.

·         Click Content settings in the "Privacy" section.

·         Click the Cookies tab in the Content Settings dialog that appears.  

Delete cookies

o    Click Show cookies and other site data.

o    To delete all cookies, click Remove all.

o    To delete a specific cookie, select the site that issued the cookie, then the cookie, and click Remove.

Block cookies by default

o    Block all cookies: Select "Block sites from setting any data." Keep in mind that selecting this setting will prevent most sites that require you to sign in from working. You'll see in the address bar whenever a cookie has been blocked.

o    Block only third-party cookies: Select the "Block all third-party cookies without exception" checkbox. Even if you've added a site to the Exceptions dialog and have chosen to allow its cookies, the site's third-party cookies won't be accepted if this checkbox is selected

Allow cookies by default

o    Make sure "Allow local data to be set" is selected to allow both first-party and third-party cookies. If you only want to accept first-party cookies, select the "Block all third-party cookies without exception" checkbox.

Cookies – SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER Web site 1stbrowser.com and services related elements (excluding the SIEN’S 1ST BROWSER application itself)

Like many websites and services, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your username and password for future logins to the Site or Application, if applicable, and to store your user preferences. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site and Application, to better understand how you interact with the Site and Application and to monitor aggregate usage by SIEN users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Application and then close your browser. A cookie does not allow us to obtain any personally identifiable information (such as your real name or address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using the Site or the Application. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Application.

**Email**

SIEN SA will offer to send an email about SIEN to your friends via our “Invite Your Friends” feature. When you invite your friends they will only receive one invitation email from you. You and your friends will not receive any additional emails from SIEN or any other third party. Your email address and you friends email addresses, when we have them stored in our database, are protected by SIEN by restricting access to the database. If you wish to remove your email address from our database you can do it by clicking the link at the end of the email you received or by writing to [support@1stbrowser.com](mailto:support@1stbrowser.com).

**Phishing**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to SIEN. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your username, password or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the US Federal Trade Commission’s website.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

**Service Providers**. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related actions (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site or Application’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Application are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**. SIEN cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of SIEN or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

**Business Transfers**. SIEN may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

All users who provide Personal Information to SIEN may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided to us by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us at [support@1stbrowser.com](mailto:support@1stbrowser.com) with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. You may also uninstall the Application at any time. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

**Security**

SIEN is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

**International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United Kingdom and choose to provide information to us, SIEN transfers Personal Information to the United Kingdom and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**Links to Other Sites**

You will be presented with and have access to links to other websites through your use of our Site and the Application. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

This Site, Application and Service are not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [contact@1stbrowser.com](mailto:contact@1stbrowser.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@1stbrowser.com](mailto:contact@1stbrowser.com).

SIEN  
Attention: Privacy Issues  
20, rue Bouvier, 75011 Paris  
Address: [support@1stbrowser.com](mailto:support@1stbrowser.com)
